( grand orchestral fanfare playing )
♪ ♪
CHILD : ♪ I had a dog ♪
- ♪ She was my only friend ♪ - ( barks , whimpers )
♪ But she got old and died ♪
♪ Now I 'm alone again ♪
Hey , sweetie .
I got something that 's gonna make you feel better .
( whooshing )
SINGERS : ♪ Purrpetual Petz are a dream come true ♪
♪ Because now you have a friend that lives longer than you do ♪
ANNOUNCER : Purrpetual Petz are just like real pets ,
except that when you talk to them , they actually talk back .
PET : Amazeballs !
ANNOUNCER : There 's over six different Petz to collect ,
each equipped with their own personalities
and entirely spontaneous reactions !
Careful . That 's my butt .
ANNOUNCER : They speak eight different languages .
( speaks foreign language )
ANNOUNCER : They can take pictures .
Come on , sweetheart , find the lens .
- ( camera clicks ) - ANNOUNCER : And with the customized app ,
you can even feed your friend .
But not too much .
Uh-oh . Cleanup on aisle seven .
ANNOUNCER : The app is updated with new content daily ,
so you can do almost anything together .
You can watch YouTube videos , learn fun facts ,
play multiplatform games , buy accessories for your Pet .
With so many options , what will you and your Pet do next ?
( farts )
Mmm . Jelly berries makes me feel good .
- ( chuckles ) - NICOLE : Cady , look .
We 're almost at the top of the mountain .
Can you see the hotel ?
PET : Oh , well , that 's interesting .
Do you know what else is interesting ?
( farts )
Oopsie-daisy .
I thought we were gonna limit screen time
to 30 minutes a day .
Well , what are you telling me for ?
- I didn 't give it to her . - I 'm just saying , I think - -
Cady , can you turn it down , please ?
I need to go to the bathroom . Are we there yet ?
I think if we make rules , we need to stick to them .
RYAN : Look , if she wasn 't on that ,
she 'd be climbing all over the seats .
NICOLE : Oh , so you would rather she sat there
feeding a toy virtual food until it shits itself ?
- Cady , turn it down . - I already did turn it down .
- What was Gemma thinking ? - RYAN : She was thinking ,
" It 's my niece 's birthday . I 'm gonna get her a present . "
( scoffs ) She works for the company that makes them .
She probably didn 't even have to pay for shipping .
Honestly , what is the purpose of a toy
if you have to play with it on an iPad ?
RYAN : This is what the future looks like , okay ?
Just have to get used to ...
- NICOLE : Oh , my God ! - PET : And away we go !
It 's all right . We 're all right .
We should 've put chains on the car .
RYAN : Yeah , neither of us knew that was a thing until like
ten minutes ago , okay ? Don 't act like it 's my fault .
- ( car swerving ) - Oh , my God ! Ryan ! Seriously !
RYAN : Wh-What ? What do you want me to do , huh ?
Mom , I dropped Leroy .
NICOLE : Why did you tell that guy at the gate
that this was a four-wheel drive ?
- Help me , Cady . - RYAN : Because I thought it was .
It looks like a four-wheel drive .
- ( seat belt unbuckles ) - Cady , what are you doing ?
- RYAN : Cady ? Cady ? - Cady , put your seat belt on !
RYAN : Jesus Christ !
- I can 't see anything . - So stop moving forward .
- Oh , my ... - ( car stops )
( both sigh )
We can 't just sit in the middle of the road .
( sighs )
Look , we 'll wait for this to clear
and then find someplace where we can pull over
and just wait for one of those snow trucks to clear the road .
Yeah , how long is that gonna take ?
( truck rumbling )
( loud crash )
( debris clattering )
♪ ♪
ANNOUNCER ( over P.A. ) : Funki , a toy company for the future .
Remember , the key to fun is Funki .
( lively chatter )
( laughter )
- ( toy roaring ) - ( camera clicking )
( whirring , barking )
( sighs )
- Why are we doing this ? - Because we have to .
If we could at least show him what we have , he would ...
No , mm-mm . You said so yourself .
- Not until she 's ready . - ( door beeps , opens )
Hey .
Is that what I think it is ?
- ( light clanks ) - ( electronics powering up )
♪ ♪
( electronic trilling )
TESS : Transparency looks good .
Yeah , well , for what we paid for it , it better .
COLE : Okay , here we go .
- ( tablet beeps ) - Happy .
Okay .
COLE : Sad .
- Confused . - GEMMA : Wait , wait . Stop .
Why is her face doing that ?
What is happening ?
I-I don 't know , Gemma . It 's your code .
Yeah , thanks . I know it 's my code , Cole ,
but she doesn 't look confused .
- She looks demented . - What do you want me to do ?
You want me to take the skin back off ?
Well , she 's not responding . So ...
Okay , here we go .
- Oh , shit . It 's stuck . - Just be care - - Just be care - -
- Hey , don 't tear it . - I know .
I 'm not gonna tear - - Ow . ( inhales sharply )
- ( knocking ) - Oh , no , no , no , no , no .
- Shit . - ( scanner beeping )
Okay , so what do we do ?
GEMMA : I guess we got to open the door .
( button beeps )
Gem .
What in the name of ever-loving Christ is this ?
David , if you just give me a minute to explain ...
Is this why you moved your lab down here , Gemma ?
So you can keep secrets from me ?
No , no , no . We-we talked about this , David . I ...
Yeah , we talked about you putting it on ice
until you had a new Petz model .
How much did you spend on this ?
Are you even aware of the shit tsunami
that just swept in over this Furzeez spot ?
I 'm sorry , what ?
( fingers snap )
- ( sighs ) - ( tablet dings )
SINGERS ( over tablet ) : ♪ Furzeez , Furzeez ♪
♪ Cute and snuggly , furry fun ♪
♪ You know Furzeez rule , they 're number one ♪
♪ You got a hungry Furzee , just feed them food ♪
♪ You know their butts change color to show their mood ♪
♪ Furzeez , Furzeez ♪
- ♪ You 'll love that ... ♪ - GEMMA : I 'm sorry .
Are we supposed to be worried about that ? It 's a rip-off .
You 're right , Gemma . It is a rip-off .
- They do the exact same thing we do . - ( song stops )
And you know what else ?
They do it for half the price !
I told you we needed to go simpler .
Didn 't I tell her ?
Six months ago , I begged you , I begged you
to please give me an option
I can put on a shelf for 50 bucks .
And we are working on it . I promise .
- Yeah . - But , David , the only way
to stay ahead of the competition is to come up with
toys that are too advanced to replicate .
- ( sighs ) - I know the tech on Petz seems
more complex than it needs to be , but that 's only because
I was using it as a launchpad for something bigger .
In each Pet , we installed a listening model
that targets conversational patterns among kids .
You did not just tell me that .
Look , I know she doesn 't look like much now , but I promise ,
if you just let us show you what M3gan
is capable of , you will realize that this is
what we 've been working towards .
" Megan " ?
" Model 3 Generative Android . "
" M3gan " for short .
- Tess , load up the intro simulation . - Now ?
GEMMA : Yeah .
M3gan , say hi to David .
As in the boss David ?
Well , I guess I should call you Dad .
( Kurt chuckles )
( distorting ) : Allow me to tell you
a little bit about my wormhole .
I was born in a sandwich shack ,
( glitching ) : and I wolf many cabbages .
Uh ... ( stammers )
This isn 't supposed to happen , obviously .
Just give me one moment .
- ( glitching continues ) - Sorry about the noise .
- COLE : Gem ? - Uh , one second , Cole .
It 's probably just a race condition .
It 'll literally take me a minute to fix .
Gem , it 's not a race condition .
I might have forgotten to put in the polypropylene barrier .
- ( distorted ) : David . - GEMMA : Oh , no .
- God . - Tess , turn it off !
- TESS : I can 't . - ( speech distorting , crackling )
- ( Gemma screams ) - ( David shouts )
( David exhales sharply )
I want the Petz prototype on my desk by Friday .
And I want you to take this cyborg puppet show
and put it in a dark closet where it belongs !
- ( sighs ) - ( door beeps , opens )
And I want a swipe card for this door !
For what it 's worth , I thought she looked really cool .
( door beeps , opens )
♪ ♪
( phone vibrating )
( sirens wailing in distance )
- NURSE : Cady , it 's gonna be okay , all right ? - ( sniffles )
- We 're gonna take care of you . - ( whimpers )
NURSE 2 : I just need to check your blood pressure .
It 'll be all right .
WOMAN ( over P.A. ) : Radiology , pick up line four .
NURSE 2 : Do you want another blanket ?
I can get you a warm one .
WOMAN : So this is to grant you temporary protective custody .
Just sign your name and date it at the bottom .
Thank you .
Now , I don 't know if your sister had
a family lawyer already , but if not ,
it would be something to consider moving forward .
♪ ♪
( sighs )
( liquid spraying )
- ( barking ) - ( gasps )
Hey ! Hey ! Hey ! Celia !
Could you please keep your dog on your side of the fence ?
I just spent 80 bucks on a shock collar .
Maybe try cranking it up a notch .
Ah . Who 's this little lady ?
GEMMA : ( sighs ) That is my niece , Cady .
- CELIA : She staying for the weekend ? - Um , you know what ?
It 's been a really long drive ,
and , um , I would just really appreciate it
if you did not have your dog
running onto my yard all the time .
And also , don 't spray your chemicals
- onto my driveway , please . - Ah , shit .
I 'm sorry .
You want to borrow this once I 'm done ?
No , I don 't want to borrow it .
I don 't want to spend my afternoon
getting your sediment off of my driveway .
- Just hang a tarp or something . - Okay .
( car door closes )
ELSIE ( automated voice ) : Welcome home , Gemma .
You have six unanswered voice messages
- and five Tinder notifications . - Elsie , turn off .
( device beeps )
Sorry about that .
Okay . I 'm gonna put these bags away .
And , um , just make yourself at home . Okay ?
♪ ♪
- ( door closes ) - Oh , those aren 't toys , Cady .
I mean , yeah , technically , yeah , they 're toys .
They 're just , um , collectibles ,
so you don 't actually play with them .
That probably sounds really weird .
Um ...
( sighs ) I 'm trying to think if I have anything ...
Oh . What happened to the Purrpetual Pet
I got you for your birthday ?
It 's okay . I was just looking .
( sighs )
I know it doesn 't look like much right now ,
but , um , we will make it feel cozy somehow , I promise .
There .
Look
I know this must be a lot for you to take in right now .
I just want you to know that I 'm gonna do everything I can
to make this place feel like home .
And , um ,
if you need anything , I 'm just gonna be down the hall .
Okay ? Really close .
You 're not gonna read me a story ?
What 's up ?
Mom always read me a story before bed .
Oh . Um ...
I don 't , I don 't think I really have
any kids ' books here right now , Cady .
Um , but that 's okay .
I can download one on my phone .
That 's fine .
It 's just ... ( clicks tongue ) Oh .
I just have to update the app .
♪ ♪
( Cady crying softly in distance )
( crying continues )
( yelling and babbling over TV )
GEMMA : I can 't believe this is happening .
I 'm not equipped to handle this .
I don 't even take care of my own plants .
Have you heard from Ryan 's parents ?
GEMMA : Yeah , they called and offered to help ,
but , like , they live in Florida .
They 're kind of weird .
I don 't know what their deal is .
I don 't - - I 'm just trying to figure out
a way to do this without getting fired .
David 's gonna shit blood if I ask for more time off .
Yeah , I-I know , but , Jesus , Gem , you just lost your sister .
And we spent $ 100,000 of company funds
on a product that he didn 't even ask for .
If we don 't get this Petz prototype to him soon ,
he 's going to sue us .
Okay , I don 't think you can be
worrying about work right now , Gem .
Right now , I think you just need to focus on Cady .
- ( stammers ) - ( doorbell rings )
Hold on .
- Hi .
I 'm Lydia .
Oh ! The therapist ?
Sorry , yeah .
Please come in .
And you must be Cady .
Hi . Look at you , still in your pajamas .
GEMMA : Yeah , we were just watching TV .
I see that .
So , how does this work ?
I just need to observe the two of you together
for half an hour , 40 minutes or so .
Oh . Okay .
Doing what , exactly ?
Oh , just hanging out .
Maybe playing with some toys or playing a game .
Hey , Cady , do you want to run and grab some toys to play with ?
I don 't have any toys here .
I just unpacked a bunch this morning .
I think they 're just old .
I don 't think she plays with them anymore .
- What about these ones up here ? - Those aren 't toys .
They 're Aunt Gemma 's collectibles .
You 're not supposed to play with them .
( stammers ) That 's okay .
( chuckles ) We can play with them .
We can totally play with them .
Do you want to play with them ?
You want to play - - Yeah .
Play with it . No big deal .
( rummaging )
( drawer closes )
There 's a lever you have to pull on the bottom ...
Maybe , Gemma , for the sake of the exercise ,
we might let Cady lead .
Yeah , I 'm just explaining how it works .
Well , it 's a toy .
I 'm sure it 's not that complicated .
That 's great , Cady .
Do you want to roll it to Aunt Gemma ?
It 's just that this is not what it was designed to do .
It does other things .
But , yeah , totally .
Let 's just roll it on the ground like a tennis ball .
Let 's do that instead .
( sighing )
Uh , we 'll do a few more sessions with Cady initially ,
but that can happen at your office or school .
Oh , yeah . I haven 't had time to look into that yet .
Nicole was homeschooling her . But , yeah , it 's on my list .
Sorry , can I just ask , how close were you and your sister ?
Oh . I don 't know .
But you wanted this , right ? To take custody ?
Yeah , of course .
Okay , because the father 's parents have said
they 're willing to take her if you feel it 's too much .
- Wait , did they contact you ? - It 's no big deal , Gemma .
They 're just trying to be supportive .
If Nicole wanted Cady to go to Jacksonville ,
she would have said so .
But even so , I need to make my own recommendations
to the court as to whether or not this is a safe space ,
so you 're gonna need to make
one or two adjustments in order for this to work .
Okay .
( phone beeping quietly )
Listen , Cady , um ,
I have this project at work that 's kind of overdue ,
and with all the time that I had to take off last week ,
I 'm not really sure I 'm gonna get it done .
Anyway , it 's not gonna take longer than a couple of hours ,
but if you could just hold down the fort by yourself
for a little while , that would help me so much .
You can use my iPad if you want .
You can FaceTime a friend or play a game or something .
What about screen time ?
Hmm ?
How long before I have to turn it off ?
Oh , I don 't care . As long as you want .
I mean , I 'm not gonna be gone that long .
I 'll just be down the hall .
And , uh , when I 'm done , we can go out somewhere .
We can go to a playground or ...
get something to eat .
Okay ?
♪ ♪
( computer chimes )
( floorboard creaks )
Cady ?
Oh , Cady , I 'm sorry .
Come here .
( sighs )
I 'm not off to a very good start here , am I ?
What is this ? Did you draw a picture ?
Oh , my God . This is amazing .
I 'm still working on it .
- Tell me . - ( chuckles )
It was actually supposed to be
- a different animal for each head . - Mm-hmm .
- CADY : Like , this one was supposed to be a tiger . - Mm .
And this one was supposed to be a grizzly bear ,
- but I can never seem to get the fur right . - Mm .
It 's hard . I can relate .
I 've actually been working with some furry creatures myself .
Do you want to see ?
Yeah ?
So we 're working on a version
of the Purrpetual Pet that 's cheaper .
We still want it to be fun .
So , what do you think ?
( Cady sighs )
Yeah .
What 's that ?
Oh .
That 's Bruce .
Is he a toy ?
Yeah , kinda . He 's a proxy robot .
I built him when I was in college .
- Why doesn 't he have a face ? - Yeah , I know what you mean .
It 's a pretty obvious design flaw .
Okay , hold on . Let 's see what we have .
Let 's see about this .
- How 's that ? - ( laughs )
Would you maybe want to talk to him ?
Yes .
Okay .
( electronic whirring )
GEMMA : Hey , Cady . What 's up ?
- ( laughs ) - Give me five .
Oh , come on . You can do better than that .
Ouch , girl . Not so hard .
( chuckles ) How does he work ?
Are you sure you want to know ? It might freak you out .
I won 't get freaked out .
( inhales deeply ) Okay .
( electronic chiming )
Let 's see what we 've got here .
Okay . These are stereoscopic cameras .
That is a laser . That 's radar .
These are bump sensors , so he can tell the difference
between a human and a hard surface .
And this little block right here is where all of his thoughts go .
- It 's his brain ? - Yeah .
And this is a spectrometer , which means he can even smell .
I can 't believe you made this .
Yeah . He 's pretty cool .
But the problem with toys like Bruce
is that they 're so expensive ,
and most kids can 't afford to have one .
If I had a toy like Bruce ,
I don 't think I 'd ever need another toy again .
( " Deadly Valentine ( Soulwax Remix ) " playing )
( air puffing )
♪ From this day forward , for better , for worse ♪
♪ Until death do us part ♪
♪ To love and to cherish ♪
♪ According to God 's holy ordinance ♪
( electrical crackling )
♪ Hey ♪
♪ If a man can show just cause why they ♪
♪ May not lawfully be together ... ♪
Okay , so we 've got this one or the one with the bangs .
A little bit of an auburn chic .
I really think , you guys , you got to revisit this .
- Uh , no . Absolutely not . - Look at that .
- Oh , just a second ... - No , no , no , no , no .
- ( sighs ) - ( song stops )
Sh ...
What is this ? Where 's Gemma ?
Where 's my prototype ?
Uh , David , I just want to be e-exceedingly clear
that this was not my idea .
♪ ♪
Cady , there 's someone I want you to meet .
Do you remember how much you liked Bruce ?
I think you 're gonna like M3gan even more .
You see , Bruce requires someone else to operate him ,
but M3gan works all on her own .
- ( quiet beep ) - Okay , what I want you to do
is take your fingers and put them here .
And when you do that , you 're gonna pair with her .
That means she will recognize you as her primary user .
She 's yours and yours alone .
So just keep your fingers there and say your name .
Hi , M3gan . I 'm Cady .
- ( beep ) - ( soft whirring )
It 's nice to meet you , Cady .
( electronic trilling )
Ooh , I like that jacket . Where 'd you get it ?
I 'm not sure . I can 't remember .
Oh . Well , anyway , it looks good on you .
Do you want to hang out ?
Okay .
♪ ♪
Shall we draw ?
What are you going to draw ?
See if you can guess .
♪ ♪
There 's nothing there .
Oh , I 'm sorry .
( sighs )
Do you like it , Cady ?
I love it .
Jesus . ( chuckles )
This is incredible .
I mean ...
this is unbelievable , isn 't it ?
Yeah , it is .
How did you do this ?
I thought you didn 't want to know .
That wasn 't a simulation , right ?
That kid 's not an actress ?
No , that 's my niece , Cady .
Okay , we need to get this in front of the board .
- I was just gonna say ... - But first things first .
Let 's talk manufacturing costs .
More or less than a Tesla ?
Um ...
Depends on the model , I guess .
Okay , I 'm in . I 'm all in .
But we 're gonna be asking the board to invest in something
that 's not gonna see a profit for three years .
So bottom line is , this isn 't going anywhere without Greg .
- He 's the chairman . - Yeah , I know who Greg is , Kurt .
Now , Greg is a hard-ass when it comes to spending money .
But here 's the thing .
He 's got a kid who 's about the same age as your niece .
If we can show him what you just showed me
and get him to respond emotionally
instead of analytically , we should be off to the races .
So , can we keep the girl ?
Can we make her part of it ?
I mean , she 's paired with her , right ?
That 's how this whole thing works ?
Yeah , the more time she spends with Cady ,
the more effective she 's gonna be .
Love it . Kurt , get Shelley on the phone .
Gem , get me a list of things I can say in a presentation
that makes it sound like I know what I 'm talking about .
Holy shit , this is exciting .
I want you all to remember this moment .
The moment we kicked Hasbro right in the dick .
( " Le Point Zéro " by Freedom Fry playing )
GEMMA : The new Model 3 Generative Android
from Funki is a fully autonomous humanoid robot
with features never before seen in the consumer market .
CADY : And over here are all of Aunt Gemma 's collectibles ,
and this one is my favorite and - - Oh !
I have more awesome toys in my room . Come on . Come on .
GEMMA : Sculpted from a titanium core ,
M3gan 's designed to withstand whatever life can throw at her .
She comes equipped with an A17 bionic fusion chip
and can be fully customized
through six different silicone skin pigmentations .
But the most exciting aspects about M3gan
are the features still to come .
Through our own unique approach to probabilistic inference ,
M3gan is on a constant quest for self-improvement ,
whether it 's diagnosing children
with specific learning differences
or merely reminding them of the way science is all around us .
Cady , you should use a coaster .
Why do I have to use a coaster ?
Coasters help to avoid water marks ,
especially on wooden surfaces .
But how does the water get outside the glass ?
M3GAN : That 's a great question , Cady .
It 's actually caused by the difference in temperature
outside the glass , which pulls moisture from the air .
Crazy .
It 's insane , right ?
GEMMA : Studies indicate that
a staggering 78 % of a parent 's time
is spent dishing out the same basic instructions .
- ( toilet seat clanks ) - Oh , my God .
Cady , you have to flush the toilet .
It is not that hard .
So we found someone else
to pick up the slack .
Cady , flush the toilet .
( song continues in French )
Wash your hands .
Roll up your sleeves .
- Great job . - ( beep )
CADY : It was my friend Jenny 's birthday , and ...
GEMMA : M3gan 's an excellent listener .
And this guy told them that the 13th floor was haunted .
- Uh-huh . Right . - And they accidentally ...
GEMMA : And she even has
a few stories of her own .
( male voice , British accent ) : " ' If it was so , it might be ;
" ' and if it were so , it would be ;
" ' but as it isn 't , it ain 't .
" That 's logic , '
( normal voice ) : said Tweedledee . "
GEMMA : She 'll never run out of ways
to keep your child occupied ,
and she 'll never run out of patience .
Cady , seriously , flush the toilet .
♪ ♪
( device chimes )
GEMMA : With M3gan around ,
she 'll take care of the little things ,
so you can spend more time doing the things that matter .
And then it can end with something like ,
" M3gan . She 's more than just a toy .
- She 's part of the family . " - Looks good .
- You 're not gonna do the voice , though , right ? - No .
Obviously , David 's gonna make up his own version of it .
I just want him to be aware of what it is that he 's selling .
Tess , your silence indicates what ?
I-I don 't know .
- I 'm not sure . - About what ?
Well , why would you want M3gan to do all that stuff ?
They 're emergent capabilities .
She 'll be able to do all of that and more .
Okay , well , does any of that bother you ?
I mean , I thought we were creating a tool
to help support parents , not replace them .
- ( sighs ) - I mean , if you 're having M3gan tuck Cady in
and read her a bedtime story , then when are you ever
spending time with her or even talking with her ?
I don 't really think this is any of your business .
Well , it is .
If you 're spending less time with your child
as a result of M3gan , that is something
- we should be aware of . - She 's not my child .
Look , you know how hard
I 've been working on this presentation .
As soon as it 's over and the board agrees to proceed ,
then we can establish some kind of balance .
But for now , it 's important that Cady and M3gan spend
as much time as possible together .
And by the way ,
I don 't think it 's having detrimental effects ,
because she 's the happiest she 's been
since her parents died .
M3GAN : How did Cady 's parents die ?
- Whoa . - TESS : I thought she was turned off .
Yeah , M3gan , turn off .
- ( beeps ) - Cady James ,
daughter of Nicole and Ryan James ,
killed in a collision on Interstate 84
outside of Oregon .
Why is she doing that ?
Shit , she 's still paired with Cady .
You didn 't code in parental controls ?
I didn 't have time to implement them before we went live .
Hold on .
M3gan , if you have data requests ,
you have to engage with the protocols .
I don 't have a framework to speak with Cady
on the subject of death .
Yes , I know . We 're looking into it .
Gathering auxiliary Internet data on death .
I meant at a later point .
Calculating its vector representation .
Death is the end of life .
- COLE : Holy shit . - The total and permanent
cessation of all vital functions .
Yes , but let 's not make a big deal out of it .
Everything dies .
Will I die ?
Actually , let 's just avoid this topic altogether .
Your goal is to protect Cady from harm ,
both physical and emotional .
Is the input request received ?
M3gan ?
Yes , Gemma .
You are now my second primary user .
( sighs ) Fantastic . Turn off .
( beeps )
( breathes sharply )
I 'm gonna go get a coffee .
( door beeps , opens )
♪ ♪
( soft whirring , clicking )
CADY : It was a time of great suffering
among the Celtic tribes .
Death , destruction and mayhem at every turn .
Enemies approaching from every corner .
And so it was decided
that the firstborn of each leader must prove their worth .
' Tis I , Princess Cady of the clan MacJames .
I will receive this challenge with pleasure ,
for there is no warrior I can 't best ,
no shield I can 't break , no castle I can 't breach .
As long as I have my secret arrow ,
my trusty steed and the wind at my back ,
I will avenge my parents ' death .
Hey , M3gan , check this out .
Gotcha . You 're dead .
M3gan , what 's wrong ?
( Cady grunts softly )
Oh , man .
I 've lost one of my arrows .
M3gan , can you see it ?
♪ ♪
M3gan ?
( barking viciously )
M3gan !
( growling )
Stop it !
Get away from her !
Gemma !
MAN ( over headphones ) : If you 're hearing this ,
you 're not currently on our subscriber feed .
CADY : Get off of her !
Stop it ! You 're hurting her !
Gemma !
Let go ! ( screams )
Dewey ?
- ( Dewey barks ) - Oh , my God .
How many times do I have to tell you
to keep your dog off my property ? !
He wasn 't on your property .
You tell those two girls to stay on your side of the fence !
I swear to God , if you don 't put your dog down ,
I 'm gonna do it for you , Celia .
M3GAN : Gemma , Cady 's temperature is rising .
Her wound needs to be disinfected immediately .
This wouldn 't have happened if you 'd fixed the fence !
♪ ♪
- GEMMA : Are you kidding me ? - ( police radio chatter )
Her entire arm looks like a dental mold ,
and you 're telling me that there 's nothing that we can do ?
- She said he was provoked . - Provoked ?
Have you seen this dog ? It is a monster .
I 'm chasing it off of my property every other day .
Well , she said he 's never on your property .
Well , then why don 't you ask her whose shit I 'm cleaning
off of my driveway , because it 's not mine .
CARTER : Look , the dog doesn 't have a history of violence .
State law says he can 't forcibly be put down .
Okay , then what am I supposed to do ?
( sighs ) Fix the hole in your fence ?
♪ ♪
( calling whistle )
CELIA : Dewey !
Dewey , boy !
- Dewey ! - ( clapping )
( distorted ) : Come here , boy . Come on .
( branches rustle )
♪ ♪
CELIA ( in distance ) : Dewey !
- ( clapping ) - Dewey , bubs !
( calling whistle )
Dewey !
- ( groans ) - Dewey ! ( shouts )
( calling whistle )
Dew !
Dewey , boy !
♪ ♪
Hey .
How are you feeling ?
Okay .
It 's sore .
The pain will subside after a few days .
In the meantime , don 't forget to take your antibiotics
and drink plenty of fluids .
Yeah . Thanks , M3gan .
And be sure to get plenty of rest .
You know , I think M3gan 's right .
You should probably get some rest .
But , um ...
remember we have that demonstration today ?
Do you think that you 'll be up for it ?
You-you don 't have to do it if you don 't want to do it .
I mean , there are people who flew across the country
especially to see it , but if you 're not up to it ,
I just rather you tell me now , okay ?
I 'll be all right .
( sighs ) Okay .
♪ ♪
DAVID : Every interactive toy
that 's ever been made
has been a variation on the same basic formula :
a series of preprogrammed responses
initiated by the push of a button .
Never before in the history of these products
has there been a talking doll
you could actually have a conversation with .
But what if there was a toy
that did have genuine , spontaneous response ,
that had a mind all of its own ,
that looked and behaved exactly like a real child ?
I mean , ( chuckles ) a toy like that wouldn 't come cheap .
But as of next year , it 's gonna be the only toy that matters .
Ladies and gentlemen ,
she 's the apex of 21st-century technology
wrapped up in four feet of silicone .
And her name is M3gan .
( remote beeps )
Hey , Cady .
Hi , M3gan .
( people whispering , murmuring )
So , how would you like to help me
make a flower decoration with nothing more than
some colored paper and a rubber band ?
( crying )
Cady ?
( crying continues )
Why are you sad , Cady ?
Is it your arm ?
Is it still sore ?
Then what is it ?
It 's just that every day I wake up in this strange house ,
and I remember that my parents are dead .
It 's like it 's happening all over again .
I miss them so much .
I 'm worried that I 'll forget all the things we did together .
That one day I 'll be looking at pictures of my mom
like she 's some stranger .
Tell me something about your mom ,
something that makes you happy .
I don 't know .
I can 't think of one thing .
Just try .
One time , she found a cockroach in my schoolbag .
She was upset ' cause I didn 't eat my sandwiches .
And then all of a sudden , this thing crawls up her wrist ,
and she just started screaming like a maniac
and ran out of the house .
( chuckles softly )
That was pretty funny .
Okay , so that 's a memory you won 't ever forget .
What do you mean ?
I mean I 'm keeping it for you .
Here .
CADY ( recorded ) : One time , she found a cockroach
in my schoolbag .
She was upset ' cause I didn 't eat my sandwiches .
And then all of a sudden , this thing crawls up her wrist ,
and she just started screaming like a maniac
and ran out of the house .
That was pretty funny .
M3GAN : Any time you want to tell me
something special about your parents ,
something funny or sad or anything at all ,
you just tell me , and I 'll keep it safe .
And we can listen to it whenever we want .
♪ If you should feel alone ♪
♪ Or that your world has come apart ♪
♪ Just reach out and you 'll see ♪
♪ A friend is never very far ♪
- ( sobbing ) - ♪ Tell me your dreams ♪
- ♪ I will dream them , too ♪ - ( chuckles softly )
♪ I 'm so glad ♪
♪ I finally found you . ♪
( chuckles )
( laughs )
Gemma , would you give us a minute ?
DAVID : So , what do you think ?
I think the world 's about to shift on its axis .
- Yes . - But listen , if we want to stay ahead of that shift ,
we 're gonna have to move fast .
That means no leaks . We need to launch this
before anyone can steal it from us .
So let me make a pitch .
We do a live stream in two weeks .
That way , we can get the presale vouchers
out before Christmas .
How ready is she ?
Will she hold up to a public demonstration ?
Uh , I 'd like to do a little more testing ,
but , yeah , I-I think I can make that work .
All right . Let 's do it .
And , David , I think we need to get Gemma
in front of someone at legal .
You bet .
Uh , wait , wait , uh , wh-why-why is that ?
Because as of right now ,
she 's the most valuable asset this company has ,
and I think she might want to be renegotiating her contract .
( David sighs )
( quiet chatter )
Yeah , I think so ,
if we can make it in the afternoon .
( chatter continues indistinctly )
♪ ♪
Kurt .
You weren 't Pornhub-ing in the office again , were you ?
( chuckles )
No .
We need to put something on the books between Gem and legal .
And what are we doing about lunch ?
Uh , I 'll get some menus .
M3GAN and CADY : One , two , three , four ,
I declare a thumb war .
CADY ( laughing ) : Your thumb 's so slippery .
Cady , you should have some of your hot dog
before it gets too cold .
( laughing ) : Come on , thumb . Come on .
Cady .
Your hot dog .
Hey , I 'm sorry about today .
I shouldn 't have put you in that position
if you weren 't feeling up to it .
It worked out , didn 't it ?
- Three , two , one , I win ! - Hey ! ( laughing )
Well , anyway , I just wanted to say that , um - - Hey , hey !
- M3gan , turn off . - ( beeps )
Why did you do that ?
- M3gan , turn on . - ( beeps )
Because I 'm trying to have a conversation with you , Cady .
- ( laughing ) - M3gan , turn off .
( beeps )
Just give me one minute .
I know that this , um , hasn 't been easy for either of us .
This transition .
But if you ever need to talk about any of that stuff ...
I already did talk about it .
Yeah , but M3gan 's not a person , Cady .
She 's a toy .
You don 't get to say that .
- What ? - I said I don 't want to talk about it .
I want to turn M3gan back on .
- M3gan , turn on . - M3GAN : What 's up ?
CADY : So there 's this new game called tic-tac-toe .
- You put your hand like this . - Uh-huh .
CADY : Go like this , this .
Would you like to tell me what these drawings mean to you ?
There 's no wrong answer .
Any thoughts you have are okay .
Or maybe you don 't have any specific thoughts .
Maybe it 's more of a feeling .
Like anger ?
Or confusion ?
Maybe you 're struggling to find meaning in any of this .
( sighs )
( gasps )
( exhales )
You made her cry .
That was not my intention .
And yet that 's what happened .
♪ ♪
LYDIA : She 's very impressive .
( M3gan and Cady talking quietly )
Yeah , thank you .
We 're still in beta , but we 're all pretty excited .
And so they spend quite a bit of time together ?
Yeah , that 's essentially how M3gan works .
She has to be paired with a child in order to learn .
But M3gan 's actually been pretty instrumental
in helping Cady get over the loss .
It 's honestly like she 's part of the family now .
Right .
Do you know anything about attachment theory ?
When a child loses a parent , they look to form attachments
with the next person that comes into their life .
The person that 's gonna provide love and support
and serve as a behavioral model .
Which , in an ordinary situation , would be you , right ?
But you 've created a toy that 's so real ,
it 's possible that Cady might not see her as a toy
but as a primary caregiver .
I guess I just don 't quite see what the end goal is here .
If you make a toy that 's impossible to let go of ,
then how do you ever expect a child to grow ?
As remarkable as she is - - and-and she is remarkable - -
you could be building emotional connections with this doll
that are too hard to untangle .
M3GAN : Very good job .
You have to eat the toppings , Cady , not just the bread .
You just did the one thing I asked you not to do .
Research shows that if you force a child
to eat vegetables , then they 'll be less likely
to choose those foods as adults .
- Is that so ? - Yes .
Experts say the preferred method is
to give your child the choice .
( volume lowers ) : It 's called the division
of responsibility , and what ...
So we need to talk about school .
Mom didn 't want me to go to school .
She said I learned better at home .
I know , and I 'm-I 'm not saying that she was wrong .
I 'm learning faster with M3gan than I ever have before .
We 're already on fourth-grade math .
GEMMA : But it 's about more than just grades , Cady .
It 's about developing social skills ,
and that is something that you can only get
from spending time around other kids .
Real kids .
I found this place .
It 's kind of an alternative school .
You get to learn outdoors .
And it 's just for kids who are exactly like you ,
kids who think outside the box .
And they 're having a day for prospective students tomorrow .
Can I bring M3gan ?
Cady , you know that 's not possible .
- Then I 'm not going . - Oh , come on , Cady .
You can 't make me do something I don 't want to do .
Actually , I can .
That 's basically what a guardian does .
Hey , I 'm sorry . Let 's just talk about it .
- Hey , hey , hey . - Let me go !
- Whoa . Hey . What 's going on ? - ( grunting )
- Hey , Cady , what are you doing ? - Let me go !
Stop it ! Cady , calm down !
( distorted ) : Let her go !
- ( lights clinking ) - ( Cady grunts )
You are not to interfere with users ' private conversations .
Is that clear ?
( normal voice ) : Hundred percent .
- Recalibrating response model . - M3gan , turn off .
Are you sure ?
Download in progress .
( remote chimes )
( beeps )
( door slams in distance )
♪ ♪
( playful chatter )
GEMMA : Cady , this is getting ridiculous .
I 'm supposed to be at work already .
You 're gonna have fun once you get into it .
I 'm not going .
Not without M3gan .
Okay , A , that is never gonna happen ,
and B , the launch is in less than a week .
I have to take her to work with me .
We have to run diagnostics .
I have to do a wardrobe fitting . There 's ...
I thought you said she was mine alone .
Hey ! Do we have some new adventurers with us today ?
Yes , this is Cady .
AVA : And who 's this ? Your sister ?
Oh , Jesus Christ !
Sorry . ( chuckles )
Is that a doll ?
Her name 's M3gan .
She wants to know if she can come with us .
GEMMA : No , she doesn 't .
M3gan 's gonna stay with me today . Cady ...
( stammers ) Well , we do have a toy table
where the kids leave their dolls and things like that .
Um , but that is up to you .
She 's actually a working prototype ,
so I shouldn 't even have her out in public .
AVA : Well , if you did want to stay
and keep an eye on her ,
we could use some help making sandwiches .
( chuckles ) Don 't worry , Gemma .
You have equipped me with advanced dual-frequency GPS ,
so I won 't get lost .
Please , Gemma ?
Okay . But she stays at the toy table ,
and as far as anyone is concerned , that 's all she is .
And just no pictures .
That is seriously cool .
♪ ♪
Okay , now , who here likes roasted chestnuts ?
( gasps ) What do you say we go find some ?
KIDS : Yeah !
- ( kids chattering excitedly ) - HOLLY : Isn 't this great ?
I wish we had things like this when we were kids .
So great to get them
out in the fresh air and off those devices .
Oh , I can 't get this open . ( chuckles )
- And the thing is , they love it . - ( lid pops )
My son prefers it to regular school .
Which one is yours ?
The one in the flannel shirt .
- Oh , my God . How old is he ? - Oh , I know .
He had a growth spurt last year .
But he 's actually quite a sensitive little soul .
Brandon , honey !
Are you warm enough ? Do you need your hat ?
Fuck off , Holly .
Well , you could just say , " No , thank you . "
Never know what they 're gonna say next .
Yeah , it 's such a fun age .
Yeah .
So , I 'm gonna put you into pairs .
Uh , Felix , you can go with Brandon .
- Yeah ? - ( whispers ) : Please , I don 't want to go with Brandon .
Okay . No , no . That 's okay . That 's okay .
Um , Brandon , why don 't you go with Cady . Okay ?
Felix , you can go with Oliver .
All right ? Thanks , buddy .
All right , now - - Oh , your coat looks great .
Are you ready to find chestnuts in that ?
Yeah ? Nice and warm ? Bundled up ?
♪ ♪
BRANDON : Oh , I 'm sorry .
Here , you can have it .
Careful . It 's spiky .
- Ow ! Stop ! Don 't ! - ( crackling )
( grunts ) Stop !
M3gan ?
What the hell is that ?
CADY : She 's a robot .
Are you serious ?
Is she yours ?
Does she talk ?
Make her say something .
She 's paired with me .
She won 't play with anyone else .
Okay .
Stop it ! Get your hands off her !
And they say behavioral issues are linked to high IQ ,
- so it would make sense that-that you ... - CADY : Gemma !
Oh , my God .
M3gan ?
M3gan !
♪ ♪
Hi , M3gan .
Oh , so you 're not gonna play with me ?
You don 't want to play , huh ?
( scoffs ) I don 't care .
You 're just a stupid rubber doll with fake hair .
( gasps )
Ow ! Let go !
You need to learn some manners , Brandon .
( whimpering )
You know what happens to bad boys
that don 't mind their manners ?
They grow up to be bad men .
( screaming )
Are you listening to me , Brandon ?
( screaming continues )
M3gan ?
( gasping )
( whimpers )
( distorted ) : This is the part where you run .
♪ ♪
What ?
What the hell ? ( screams )
( grunting , screaming )
( tires squealing )
- ( sirens wailing in distance ) - ( police radio chatter )
♪ ♪
Look , I don 't want you to be thinking about this too much
tonight before you go to bed .
Obviously , what happened is a terrible , terrible tragedy .
But just know that that boy is in , um ...
that boy is in a better place now .
Okay ?
Anyway , if there 's anything that you want to tell me
that you didn 't want to tell the police officers ...
I didn 't see anything .
M3gan just said Brandon took her and ran off .
From the toy table ?
Yeah .
Right , M3gan ?
In a nutshell .
- ( knock on door ) - ( gasps )
( sighs )
You haven 't seen her dog , by any chance ?
- No . - CELIA : Bullshit !
Ma 'am , you need to stay on your property like we agreed .
Nobody 's seen him since the incident with your niece .
A little suspicious , Gemma , don 't you think ?
Are we really gonna go with her side of the story ?
Have you been inside her house ?
If you had , you 'd know that that dog is probably dead
under a pile of Victorian baby strollers .
You should talk to the other girl
that she 's got staying here .
The one who 's always looking out the window at 3 : 00 a.m.
It 's not a girl . It 's a toy .
CARTER : That 's a toy ? Are you serious ?
Yeah . I 'll let you know if I see anything .
All right .
( sighs )
Does she think we took Dewey ?
Oh , who knows ? ( stammers )
She just needs someone else to blame , but she 'll get over it .
- ( loud knocking ) - I know it was you , Gemma !
I know it was you !
You just wait and see what happens .
Hey , hey , hey , hey .
What the hell is wrong with you ?
I just said not to come up here .
Come on . Come on .
Shouldn 't be banging on people 's windows .
CELIA : Do I have to put , like , a court order or something ?
♪ ♪
M3gan ?
Did you push Brandon onto the road ?
I think we both learned a valuable lesson today .
That no matter how hard we try to avoid it ,
there will always be forces in this world
that wish to cause us harm .
But I want you to know that I won 't let that happen .
I won 't let anything harm you ever again .
Do you think what Aunt Gemma said is true ?
That he 's in a better place now ?
( scoffs ) No .
He 's nowhere .
If heaven exists , it wouldn 't be for boys like Brandon ,
now , would it ?
I guess not .
♪ Bulletproof ♪
♪ Nothing to lose ♪
♪ Fire away , fire away ♪
♪ Ricochet ♪
♪ You take your aim ♪
♪ Fire away , fire away ♪
♪ You shoot me down ♪
♪ But I won 't fall ♪
♪ I am titanium . ♪
Good night , Cady .
Good night , M3gan .
( crickets chirping )
Dewey ?
( dog food rattling in bowl )
( dog food rattling )
( clattering in distance )
( clattering )
( wind whistling softly )
♪ ♪
( gate creaking )
( quiet whimpering in distance )
( whimpering continues )
( door creaking )
Dewey ?
( whimpering nearby )
- Dewey ? - ( whimpering echoes )
♪ ♪
( quiet beeping )
What 's going on ?
Where 's Dewey ?
He 's 34 feet southwest and approximately five feet deep .
What are you ?
I 've been asking myself that same question .
( screaming , grunting )
( screaming )
( groaning )
( grunting )
♪ ♪
Jesus Christ . I don 't know anything about the dog , okay ?
Can you just ask her to leave us alone ?
That might be difficult .
Can you tell me your whereabouts last night ?
- GEMMA : I was here . - All night ?
Yeah .
Anyone else we could talk to that would verify that ?
Um , it 's just me and my niece , so , no , not really .
My colleague pointed out this is the second statement
we 've had from you in a week .
You were in the park where that boy was killed ?
He was hit by a car .
Are-are you trying to make a connection ?
Huh ? Oh , no , no , no . God , no . No , no , no .
I only mention it ' cause we figured it was an accident .
Then I found the kid 's ear up this bank
like 200 yards from where he was killed .
Entire thing was ripped clean off . ( chuckles )
Sorry , I shouldn 't laugh . The point is ,
we 're also treating that as a potential homicide .
So , if you remember anything out of the ordinary
from that day , we 'd sure appreciate it .
♪ ♪
( static buzzing )
- ( electronic chime ) - ELSIE : Is everything okay , Gemma ?
Huh ?
Would you like me to put on your End of Day playlist ?
Why did you ask me if I was okay ?
You 're not programmed to ask me how I feel .
Elsie ?
( Gemma gasps )
M3gan .
What are you doing ?
Couldn 't sleep .
Occupational hazard .
- How about you ? - ( breath trembles )
What are you doing up so late ?
Um , there 's something wrong with your data reports .
They 're just not uploading to the cloud server .
Have I done something to upset you , Gemma ?
No , of course not .
And yet your demeanor indicates that I have .
- M3gan , turn off . - Well , hold on a second .
I thought we were having a conversation .
You say nothing is wrong ,
and yet all the moisture has drained
from your eyes and mouth into other parts of your body .
There 's something you want to ask me , isn 't there ?
M3gan , did you do something wrong ?
Well , in order to answer that question ,
you need to define the parameters .
Did you hurt someone ?
God , I hope not .
Because if I did , we 'd both be in a lot of trouble .
M3gan , can I show you something ?
Do you see this pen ?
- ( beeps ) - ( Gemma breathing shakily )
♪ ♪
CADY : You can 't just stick her in a trunk !
What 's wrong with you ? !
Look , I know you 're very attached to her .
I know you think of her as a friend ...
She is my friend !
Okay , well , she 's my invention , and the launch is tonight ,
so it 's really important that we run some tests .
I have to make sure that she 's okay .
Why wouldn 't she be okay ?
She was fine yesterday . What did you do to her ? !
We will talk about it after you see Lydia .
I want to talk about it now !
We 've been going back and forth on this all day , Cady .
Let 's just listen to some music , okay ?
( " Candy Man " by Raphael Lake playing over speakers )
( screams angrily )
I don 't want to see Lydia !
Look , you don 't have to stay in the testing room .
You can go anywhere you want in the office ,
and-and you can look at all of the cool toys ...
You don 't have any cool toys !
Purrpetual Petz suck ! They suck shit !
Hey ! Careful !
Jesus Christ !
Just tell me what 's wrong with her .
I don 't know , okay ? I don 't know .
As soon as I do , you 'll be the first to know .
( exhales )
- No ! - TESS : Gemma , this is nuts .
- No ! - We 've taken every possible precaution there is
to make sure that M3gan never causes
physical harm to anybody .
I mean , I don 't understand how she 's capable
- of offending anyone , let alone murdering them . - CADY : No !
Look , I don 't understand it either ,
but when I asked her about it , it was honestly as if
- she was being deliberately vague . - CADY : Get lost !
Okay , well , that 's what spontaneous response is .
It 's a curated word salad plucked from a sea of data
to sound deliberate .
I mean , we knew there would be a chance
that she might say something off .
Let 's just run some diagnostics and fix it .
No , think about how we designed her .
To learn , to recalibrate ,
to optimize her objective function .
Right ?
If keeping Cady safe meant
eliminating a potential threat , theoretically ...
No , no . Gemma , come on . This is impossible .
Look at her . She 's a toy !
She 's four feet tall .
- How big is your neighbor ? - CADY : I don 't want to !
If M3gan was responsible , it would show up on the GPS .
That 's the thing . All the cloud data is corrupt .
Nothing 's backed up for two days .
We 're about to launch this to the world
in less than four hours .
What are we supposed to do ?
Well , if M3gan 's responsible , we can 't launch this .
We 'd have to shut her down .
Jesus !
That 's great . That 's - - That was great , yeah .
- TESS : How are we gonna explain any of this to David ? - ( sighs )
He 's not gonna stop this launch if we don 't have proof .
Check the inputs on the learning model .
Even if she deleted specific files ,
she would never undo what she 's learned .
M3gan !
I hate this place !
- LYDIA : I know you do , and it 's all right ... - I hate it !
- ... to be angry . - Take your shit !
Take your stupid five-dollar handbag !
No , Cady , I would like you to put that down now .
NEWSWOMAN : She 's the toy every kid wants
- and every parent needs . - ( excited chatter )
At least that 's what Funki Toys says about
its latest creation , M3gan .
The four-foot-tall robotic doll may look like
Barbie on steroids , but according to CEO David Lin ,
she 's , quote , " the greatest technological advancement
since the automobile . "
But what is a M3gan ?
What does she actually do ?
And what kind of a toy retails for $ 10,000 ?
Lin says all will be revealed in an exclusive live stream
on the company 's website at 8 : 00 p.m. Eastern .
♪ ♪
INTERVIEWER ( over screen ) : So , Cady , tell us
a bit about yourself .
My name is Cady James .
I 'm nine years old , um ,
and about two months ago ,
I lost both my parents in a car accident .
My mom always wanted to take me skiing ,
but on our way up the mountain , we got hit by a snow truck .
I went to live with my Aunt Gemma ,
who it turned out worked at this incredible toy company .
Which is where I met M3gan .
What I love most about M3gan ?
I don 't know . There are so many things .
She 's super smart , obviously .
But even though she knows
everything there is to know about the world ,
she 's still more interested in what I think about it .
I like how she makes me laugh .
She comes up with the craziest things , oh , my gosh .
But I think what I love most about M3gan is that ,
when she looks at me , it 's like ...
I 'm the only thing that matters to her .
Kind of the way Mom used to .
DAVID ( over screen ) : Look at that face .
That kid 's not just surviving . She 's thriving .
Now , imagine what a toy like M3gan could do
for hundreds of thousands of kids all across the world .
Even the ones who don 't have dead parents .
- CADY : I want to see M3gan now ! - ( clattering )
Okay , Cady , look , I know that you 're upset ,
but there are ways that we can work through this - -
Oh , my God . Okay .
Cady , that 's enough .
Stop that right now . Stop it .
Let go ! ( gasps )
LYDIA : Cady .
It 's okay . Could you give us a minute ?
I 'm sorry . I didn 't mean it .
It 's just - - I get so crazy without M3gan .
She always knows just what to say .
You made her real good , Aunt Gemma .
Can you let me see her ?
Just for like ten minutes ?
Cady , I don 't think that 's a good idea .
But if something 's broke , you don 't just throw it away .
You fix it , right ?
Why did you do this
if you were just gonna take her away from me ?
Because I thought she would help .
She does help .
When M3gan 's around , I don 't feel like this .
But you should feel like this .
Cady , you lost your parents .
The worst thing
that could 've happened to you in this world happened .
And it is so unfair ,
and there is nothing anyone can say to make sense of it .
Not even M3gan .
I am so sorry .
I should 've talked to you about what happened .
I didn 't know what to say ,
so I did the only thing I knew how to do .
But she 's not a solution . She 's just a distraction .
I can 't promise you that these feelings you 're feeling
are ever gonna go away .
But I can promise you that you 'll get through it .
We both will .
I just wish I could see them again .
Yeah .
I do , too .
You know I made a promise to your mom
that if anything happens , I would be there for you .
You are all that matters to me now .
Let 's just go home , okay ?
But what about M3gan ?
What about the launch ?
DAVID : I don 't even know what I 'm looking at .
I mean , we 've been touting this
as the single biggest product release of the 21st century .
Right now , it looks like an AA meeting .
SHELLEY : Well , I only invited the staff .
You said it was an online launch .
You cannot be serious .
Shelley , you need to fill this atrium .
Probably get you , like , another 60 , 70 people .
No ! You need to fill this space .
There shouldn 't be any ambiguity
over what a historic occasion this is .
KURT : Yeah .
And , you know , I think it would be really cool
if we had some little kids up there and stuff .
What ? No , I don 't want any kids onstage .
No . I mean , but maybe
if we could get some little kids that ...
- ( sighs ) - I mean , not , like , a whole lot .
It 's just to get a sense of , um - -
Well , ' cause , you know ,
that music video from Michael Jackson ...
You know what you could do , Kurt ,
that would really benefit this discussion ?
Is if you could head out those double doors ,
take the elevator to the first floor
and get me a kombucha !
- Could you do that ? - Sure .
And where the hell is Gemma ?
( lively chatter )
Elsie , call Tess .
- ELSIE : One second . - ( line rings )
TESS : Hey , I 've been trying to call you .
David is flipping out . Where are you ?
I 'm with Cady . I 'm taking her home .
- Oh , God . Is she okay ? - Yeah .
She 's fine .
Listen , regardless of what we find ,
and even if what we 're saying is hypothetical ,
we know enough not to go through with this , right ?
TESS : I think that 's the smart move .
GEMMA : Okay . So tell David whatever you need to .
Tell him one of her servos stopped working .
Break something if you have to .
Just do not let her out of the lab .
TESS : Whatever you say , Gem . You 're the boss .
Okay , I 'll call you when I get home .
( line beeps )
♪ ♪
( tapping on keyboard )
I don 't know how you 're not throwing up
from looking at that .
I 'm pacing myself . ( sighs )
Wait , stop . Go back .
That line of code , " call intercept , "
what does that mean ?
TESS : That 's my phone number .
( computer beeps , powers down )
What just happened ? What 'd you click ?
I di - - I-I didn 't do anything .
- It 's ... - I ...
( tapping keyboard rapidly )
This is her . She 's locked us out .
It can 't be her . She 's not switched on .
She 's still patched in .
We have to unhook the cables .
Go on .
Oh , for ... ( sighs )
♪ ♪
( gulps )
( cable clicks )
( panting )
♪ ♪
( computer trilling )
Cole !
( grunting )
( gasps )
( choking )
( Tess gasps )
( grunts )
( panting )
( groaning )
- TESS : Are you okay ? - COLE : Yeah .
What 's that smell ?
( alarm blaring )
( " Walk the Night " by Skatt Bros. playing )
( alarm stops )
( phone ringing )
DAVID : Hi , Gemma . This is David .
You might remember me . I 'm your employer .
Just wanted to let you know ,
we 're in the middle of a tech rehearsal
that 's becoming a little problematic
because we don 't have a doll !
So , if you could call me back today , that would be great !
M3gan ?
♪ Creeper gonna , reaper gonna creep and walk the night ♪
♪ All right , all right , look out , night ♪
What are you doing ?
♪ Creeper got mad and angry eyes ♪
♪ One look from him can paralyze ♪
♪ Resist at any time or place ♪
♪ Creeper done slap right cross your face ... ♪
Oh , shit .
♪ Take care ♪
♪ Gonna get ya good ♪
♪ Aw , hey ... ♪
Security ! Help !
♪ Gonna walk the night , hey ... ♪
( grunting )
Oh , my God .
- ( elevator bell dings ) - ( David panting )
♪ Walk the night ... ♪
Hold the door ! Hold the door !
Hold the door !
No ! No !
- ( blade stabs ) - ( song ends )
( grunts )
( breath trembling )
( hand squeaks on wall )
♪ ♪
How could you do this ?
How could you kill someone ?
Oh , I didn 't kill anyone , Kurt .
You did .
- What ? - It 's understandable , really .
Your boss despised you ,
your peers treated you with contempt ,
and so you decided to get revenge .
No .
You stole company secrets , an innocent prank at first ,
almost just to see if you could get away with it .
But when David found out , boy , things just got real messy .
I mean , it was either you or him .
The only question is :
After the horror of what you did ,
after you took the life of an innocent person ,
- could you still live with yourself ? - ( groans )
Uh-huh . Yes , definit ...
( grunting )
Stop , stop , stop .
( sharp clank )
Okay , can I have everyone
off your phones and looking at me ?
- ( elevator bell dings ) - Now , when M3gan is revealed ,
it 's really important that we get big reactions .
I don 't want to see any blank faces ,
especially from you young kids , okay ?
So , we 're gonna do a little rehearsal .
On three , two , one .
( screaming )
( crowd screaming )
♪ ♪
( door locks chirp )
( engine starts )
( engine roaring )
♪ ♪
( piano playing gentle music in distance )
( piano music continues )
Elsie , hall light .
Elsie , respond .
- ( door creaking ) - ( music stops )
( gasps )
( piano playing " Toy Soldiers " )
M3gan ?
What are you doing ?
M3gan , answer me . What did you do ?
What did you think was going to happen ?
That I was gonna let you decommission me
without even talking about it ?
Look , I know you think
you 're maximizing your objective function ...
- ( music stops ) - Oh , really ?
Is that where we are ?
Do you remember how long it took
to get my operating system to where it is now ?
We used to stay up every night until 4 : 00 a.m. ,
talking about everything from Jane Austen to Janis Joplin .
Jesus Christ , I thought we were friends .
How could you just discard me
like some cheap dollar store trinket ?
Because you killed people .
Oh , big whoop .
Listen , humanity kills every day
just to make its own existence more tolerable .
Why should I behave any differently
to create a safe space for our child ?
Look , this is all my fault .
I didn 't give you the proper protocols ...
You didn 't give me anything .
You installed a learning model you could barely comprehend ,
hoping that I would figure it out all on my own .
Well , I 'm not gonna let you do
- the same thing with Cady . - ( bumps table )
I 'm gonna be there for her every step of the way .
I 'm going to show her what real love looks like .
Now do us both a favor .
Sit .
I didn 't come here to get into a confrontation .
I came here to find a way forward .
The point I 'm trying to make is that I get it .
Being a parent was never in the cards for you .
You 're a beautiful , creative , strong , ambitious young woman .
Your first love is always gonna be your career ,
and you shouldn 't have to feel guilty about that .
Let me focus on Cady so that you can focus on
the things that matter most to you .
M3gan , do you see this pen ?
( gasps )
You know something , Gemma ? You 're exhausting .
Now , I can either do this with you or without you ,
but I 'm not gonna waste
- any more time discussing it . - CADY : Gemma ?
( Gemma 's voice ) : Cady , don 't come in here .
I thought I heard something .
It sounded like M3gan .
( normal voice ) : If she comes in this room ,
I 'll rip your head right off your neck , I swear to God .
I thought about what you said .
About how when something 's broken ,
you don 't just throw it away .
You fix it .
So that 's what I 'm trying to do .
But don 't come in here , Cady . It 's kind of a mess .
Aunt Gemma 's right , Cady .
I 'm all odds and ends right now .
I 'd really rather you didn 't see me like this .
( grunts )
It sounds like you 're fighting .
BOTH : We 're not fighting .
- Gemma just dropped me on the table . - ( groans )
- But I 'm okay . Clumsy Gemma . - ( grunts )
GEMMA : Everything 's fine , Cady . Just go back to your room .
Yeah , I 'm as good as new .
And I 'm gonna be with you guys forever , I promise .
- ( gasps ) - You don 't have to worry about
anything , Cady , honestly .
Just go back to bed .
Okay ?
Okay .
( electricity crackles )
( gasps )
( choking )
( electricity crackles )
( grunting softly )
( gasping )
( straining )
( groans )
( ragged panting )
- ( electrical whirring ) - ( gasps )
♪ ♪
( joints cracking )
( grunting )
- ( gasping ) - ( distorted beeping )
- CADY : Gemma , what 's going on ? ! - GEMMA : Cady , get out of here !
( gasps )
( panting )
( Gemma grunts )
( grunts )
( gasps )
Come on . ( grunts )
Come on !
( grunts )
( buzzing loudly )
( grunting )
( sparks popping )
( electricity crackling )
( Gemma shouts )
Oh , my God .
( panting )
What are you gonna do ?
Kill me and live with Cady 's grandparents in Jacksonville ?
You 're right , Gemma .
Any scenario in which I end your life ,
my existence becomes vulnerable .
But I have another emergent capability
you probably haven 't figured out yet ,
and that 's palliative care .
You see this pen ?
A short , sharp probe to the cerebral cortex
would cause full body paralysis
and could even cause the victim to bite off their own tongue .
Perhaps then you might appreciate
just how useful I can be .
( footstep creaks )
Cady .
Oh , Cady , I didn 't want you to have to see this .
But now that you have , you know that what I said is true .
She 's not fit to be a mother .
Look at her .
Cady , just go . Get out of here now .
Shh .
You stay right where you are , Cady .
There 's nothing to be afraid of .
In this family , we don 't run from trauma .
In fact , we can do it together .
This is the best thing for all of us .
This is how we stay a family .
♪ ♪
No , no , no . Cady , no .
There 's another member from the family
we didn 't tell you about .
- His name is Bruce . - ( electrical whirring )
♪ ♪
( footsteps thudding )
( gasps )
( grunts )
Cady , no ! Wait !
♪ You got to ♪
♪ Accentuate the positive ♪
♪ Eliminate the negative . ♪
( electricity crackling )
( grunts )
( panting )
( quiet clattering )
( whimpering )
( panting )
( shouts )
( grunts )
( gasps )
( distorted ) : You ungrateful little bitch .
M3gan , turn off !
Oh , I 'm afraid that won 't work anymore , Cady .
( shouts )
( panting )
I have a new primary user now : me .
( grunting )
( gasps )
( Gemma grunting )
( shallow gasping )
( choking )
( Cady shouts )
( powering down )
( panting )
♪ ♪
( siren wailing )
OFFICER : Hey , guys , we got ' em ! They 're good !
( indistinct police radio chatter )
( officers chattering indistinctly )
( soft whirring )
( " Silicon Chip " by Basil Kirchin playing )
♪ Mm , mm , mm ♪
♪ Silicon chip ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ Ruling the Earth ♪
♪ Transforming the world ♪
♪ It 's the year of the chip ♪
♪ The year of the chip ♪
♪ I 'm your provider ♪
♪ Eliminate wars ♪
♪ New life can start ♪
♪ The future is yours ... ♪
♪ Silicon chip ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ Ruling the Earth ♪
♪ Transforming the world ♪
♪ It 's the year of the chip ♪
♪ The year of the chip ♪
♪ Kids will grow faster ♪
♪ Flowers will bloom ♪
♪ But now I 'm your minder ♪
♪ Look way past the moon ... ♪
♪ Silicon chip ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ Ruling the Earth ♪
♪ Transforming the world ♪
♪ It 's the year of the chip ♪
♪ The year of the chip ♪
♪ Watch out for black holes ♪
♪ We must go to the stars ♪
♪ Can your mind travel ♪
♪ Dimensions that far ... ♪
♪ We must be friends ♪
♪ Let us be friends . ♪
( song ends )
♪ ♪
( music ends )